Bell Brothers Collection
Bell Brothers Collection
- Phonograph records
  - Mendelssohn: Preludes and Fugue E Minor, Op. 35, 2, Ralph Leopold; Mendelssohn: Passion, 4, undated; bell_brothers_056; lacquer on glass disc
  - Mephisto Waltz, Bastan (Part 3), undated; bell_brothers_225; shellac disc
  - Metropolitan Opera - Spanish: La Traviata (Parts 1 and 3), 12/05/1942; bell_brothers_745; lacquer on glass disc
  - Metropolitan Opera - Spanish: La Traviata (Parts 2 and 4), 12/05/1942; bell_brothers_746; lacquer on glass disc
  - Metropolitan Opera - Spanish: La Traviata (Parts 5 and 7), 12/05/1942; bell_brothers_747; lacquer on glass disc
  - Metropolitan Opera - Spanish: La Traviata (Part 6), 12/05/1942; bell_brothers_748; lacquer on glass disc
  - Metropolitan Opera - Spanish: La Traviata (Parts 8 and 10), 12/05/1942; bell_brothers_749; lacquer on glass disc
  - Metropolitan Opera - Spanish: La Traviata (Part 12), 12/05/1942; bell_brothers_750; lacquer on glass disc
  - Metropolitan Opera - Spanish: La Traviata (Part 13), 12/05/1942; bell_brothers_751; lacquer on glass disc
  - Metropolitan Opera: [title is unknown] (Part 2), 05/12/1939; bell_brothers_727; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Metropolitan Opera: [title is unknown] (Parts 1 and 3), 05/12/1939; bell_brothers_726; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Metropolitan Opera: Aida (Intermission - 1st and 2nd), 03/02/1940; bell_brothers_702; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Metropolitan Opera: Aida (Intermission - 3rd), 03/02/1940; bell_brothers_703; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Metropolitan Opera: Aida (Parts 1 and 3), 03/02/1940; bell_brothers_694; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Metropolitan Opera: Aida (Parts 2 and 4), 03/02/1940; bell_brothers_695; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Metropolitan Opera: Aida (Parts 5 and 7), 03/02/1940; bell_brothers_696; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Metropolitan Opera: Aida (Parts 6 and 8), 03/02/1940; bell_brothers_697; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Metropolitan Opera: Aida (Parts 9 and 11), 03/02/1940; bell_brothers_698; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Metropolitan Opera: Aida (Parts 10 and 12), 03/02/1940; bell_brothers_699; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Metropolitan Opera: Celestia Aida (Part 13), 03/02/1940; bell_brothers_700; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Metropolitan Opera: Celestia Aida (Part 14), 03/02/1940; bell_brothers_701; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Metropolitan Opera: Barbiere Di Siviglia (Act 1 (a)), 12/16/1950; bell_brothers_125; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Metropolitan Opera: Barbiere Di Siviglia (Act 3), 12/16/1950; bell_brothers_128; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Metropolitan Opera: Carmen (Part 1, Act 1), 01/31/1952; 02/16/1952; bell_brothers_121; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Metropolitan Opera: Carmen (Part 2, Act 1 and Part 4, Act 2), 01/31/1952; 02/16/1952; bell_brothers_122; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Metropolitan Opera: Carmen (Part 3, Act 1 and Act 2 and Part 6, Act 3), 01/31/1952; 02/16/1952; bell_brothers_123; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Metropolitan Opera: Carmen (Part 5, Act 3 and Part 7, Act 4), 01/31/1952; 02/16/1952; bell_brothers_124; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Metropolitan Opera: Carmen (Parts 1 and 3), 03/15/1941; bell_brothers_705; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Metropolitan Opera: Carmen (Parts 2 and 4), 03/15/1941; bell_brothers_706; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Metropolitan Opera: Carmen (Parts 5 and 7), 03/15/1941; bell_brothers_707; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Metropolitan Opera: Carmen (Parts 6 and 8), 03/15/1941; bell_brothers_708; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Metropolitan Opera: Carmen (Parts 9 and 11), 03/15/1941; bell_brothers_709; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Metropolitan Opera: Carmen (Parts 10 and 12), 03/15/1941; bell_brothers_710; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Metropolitan Opera: Carmen (Part 13), 03/15/1941; bell_brothers_711; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Metropolitan Opera: Carmen (Part 14), 03/15/1941; bell_brothers_712; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Metropolitan Opera: Carmen (Parts 1 and 2), 04/17/1937; bell_brothers_713; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Metropolitan Opera: Carmen (Parts 3 and 4), 04/17/1937; bell_brothers_714; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Metropolitan Opera: Carmen (Part 5), 04/17/1937; bell_brothers_715; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Metropolitan Opera: Don Carlo (Act 1, Scene 1 - 1), 11/06/1950; bell_brothers_130; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Metropolitan Opera: Don Carlo (Act 1, Scene 2 - 2 and Act 1, Scene 2 - 3), 11/06/1950; bell_brothers_146; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Metropolitan Opera: Don Carlo (Act 2, Scene 1 - 4 and Act 2, Scene. 2 - 5), 11/06/1950; bell_brothers_147; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Metropolitan Opera: Don Carlo (Act 3, Scene 1 - 6 and Act 3, Scene 2 - 7), 11/06/1950; bell_brothers_148; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Metropolitan Opera: Don Carlo (Act 4, No. 8 and Conclusion, No. 9), 11/06/1950; bell_brothers_149; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Metropolitan Opera: Don Pasquale (Parts 1 and 3), 12/21/1940; bell_brothers_738; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Metropolitan Opera: Don Pasquale (Parts 2 and 4), 12/21/1940; bell_brothers_739; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Metropolitan Opera: Don Pasquale (Parts 5 and 7), 12/21/1940; bell_brothers_740; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Metropolitan Opera: Don Pasquale (Parts 6 and 8), 12/21/1940; bell_brothers_741; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Metropolitan Opera: Don Pasquale (Parts 9 and 11), 12/21/1940; bell_brothers_742; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Metropolitan Opera: Don Pasquale (Part 10), 12/21/1940; bell_brothers_743; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Metropolitan Opera: Don Pasquale (Part 12), 12/21/1940; bell_brothers_744; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Metropolitan Opera: Faust (Parts 1 and 3), 01/30/1943; bell_brothers_752; lacquer on glass disc
  - Metropolitan Opera: Faust (Parts 2 and 4), 01/30/1943; bell_brothers_753; lacquer on glass disc
  - Metropolitan Opera: Faust (Parts 5 and 7), 01/30/1943; bell_brothers_754; lacquer on glass disc
  - Metropolitan Opera: Faust (Parts 6 and 8), 01/30/1943; bell_brothers_755; lacquer on glass disc
  - Metropolitan Opera: Faust (Parts 9 and 11), 01/30/1943; bell_brothers_756; lacquer on glass disc
  - Metropolitan Opera: Faust (Parts 10 and 12), 01/30/1943; bell_brothers_757; lacquer on glass disc
  - Metropolitan Opera: Faust (Part 13), 01/30/1943; bell_brothers_758; lacquer on glass disc
  - Metropolitan Opera: Götterdämmerung (Part 1, Act 1), 02/17/1951; bell_brothers_131; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Metropolitan Opera: Götterdämmerung (Parts 2 and 3, Act 1), 02/17/1951; bell_brothers_132; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Metropolitan Opera: Götterdämmerung (Part 4, Act 1 and Part 7 Act 2), 02/17/1951; bell_brothers_133; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Metropolitan Opera: Götterdämmerung (Part 5, Act 1 and Part 6 Act 2), 02/17/1951; bell_brothers_134; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Metropolitan Opera: Götterdämmerung (Part 8, Act 3 and Part 10, Act 3), 02/17/1951; bell_brothers_135; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Metropolitan Opera: Götterdämmerung (Part 9, Act 3), 02/17/1951; bell_brothers_136; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Metropolitan Opera: Intermission (Part 1, 2nd and Part 1, 3rd), 02/10/1940; bell_brothers_728; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Metropolitan Opera: Intermission (Part 2, 2nd and Part 2, 3rd), 02/10/1940; bell_brothers_729; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Metropolitan Opera: Marriage of Figaro (1st and 2nd Intermissions, Part 1), 03/09/1940; bell_brothers_724; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Metropolitan Opera: Marriage of Figaro (2nd and 3rd Intermission, Part 2), 03/09/1940; bell_brothers_725; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Metropolitan Opera: Marriage of Figaro (Parts 1 and 3), 03/09/1940; bell_brothers_716; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Metropolitan Opera: Marriage of Figaro (Parts 2 and 4), 03/09/1940; bell_brothers_717; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Metropolitan Opera: Marriage of Figaro (Parts 5 and 7), 03/09/1940; bell_brothers_718; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Metropolitan Opera: Marriage of Figaro, (Parts 6 and 8), 03/09/1940; bell_brothers_719; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Metropolitan Opera: Marriage of Figaro, (Parts 9 and 11), 03/09/1940; bell_brothers_720; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Metropolitan Opera: Marriage of Figaro (Parts 10 and 12), 03/09/1940; bell_brothers_721; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Metropolitan Opera: Marriage of Figaro (Parts 13 and 15), 03/09/1940; bell_brothers_722; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Metropolitan Opera: Marriage of Figaro (Part 14), 03/09/1940; bell_brothers_723; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Metropolitan Opera: Television Broadcast (Parts 1 and 3), 03/10/1940; bell_brothers_730; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Metropolitan Opera: Television Broadcast (Parts 2 and 4), 03/10/1940; bell_brothers_731; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Midsummer Night’s Dream, WNYC The Shakespeare Festival, Shakespeare Theater (Parts 1 and 2), 03/03/1952; bell_brothers_438; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Midsummer Night’s Dream, WNYC The Shakespeare Festival, Shakespeare Theater (Parts 3 and 4), 03/03/1952; bell_brothers_439; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Miliza Korjus, undated; bell_brothers_066; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Monroe Silver: Cohen Talks About the Ladies, undated; bell_brothers_250; shellac disc
  - Monteverdi: 1. Lagrimo Occhi Mici; 2. Madrigal Ohimé Dov' e il Moi ben, Maria Castellazzi, Leila Ben Sedira, (Disc 1), undated; bell_brothers_372; vitrolac disc
  - Monteverdi: 1. Maledetto; 2. Madrigal Chiome d'ore, Maria Castellazzi, Leila Ben Sedira, (Disc 2), undated; bell_brothers_373; vitrolac disc
  - Montreal Festivals Orchestra: Ave Verum, undated; bell_brothers_363; vitrolac disc
  - Montreal Festivals Orchestra: Requiem 1. Introit et Kyrie (Part 1), undated; bell_brothers_354; vitrolac disc
  - Montreal Festivals Orchestra: Requiem 1. Introit et Kyrie (Part 2), undated; bell_brothers_355; vitrolac disc
  - Montreal Festivals Orchestra: Requiem 2. Offertoire (Part 1), undated; bell_brothers_356; vitrolac disc
  - Montreal Festivals Orchestra: Requiem 2. Offertoire (Part 2), undated; bell_brothers_357; vitrolac disc
  - Montreal Festivals Orchestra: Requiem 3. Sanctus, undated; bell_brothers_358; vitrolac disc
  - Montreal Festivals Orchestra: Requiem 4. Pie Jesu, undated; bell_brothers_359; vitrolac disc
  - Montreal Festivals Orchestra: Requiem 5. Agnus Dei, undated; bell_brothers_360; vitrolac disc
  - Montreal Festivals Orchestra: Requiem 6. Libera Me, undated; bell_brothers_361; vitrolac disc
  - Montreal Festivals Orchestra: Requiem 7. In Paradisum, undated; bell_brothers_362; vitrolac disc
  - Mozart: Concerto in E Flat, Serkin (Part 1), undated; bell_brothers_282; vitrolac disc
  - Mozart: Concerto in E Flat, Serkin (Part 2), undated; bell_brothers_283; vitrolac disc
  - Mozart: Concerto in E Flat, Serkin (Part 3), undated; bell_brothers_284; vitrolac disc
  - Mozart: Concerto in E Flat, Serkin (Part 4), undated; bell_brothers_285; vitrolac disc
  - Mozart: Concerto in E Flat, Serkin (Part 5), undated; bell_brothers_286; vitrolac disc
  - Mozart: Concerto in E Flat, Serkin (Part 6), undated; bell_brothers_287; vitrolac disc
  - Mozart: Die Zauberflöte - Bei Männern, E. Rethberg, E. Pinza, undated; bell_brothers_222; shellac disc
  - Mozart: Sonata in E Flat Major, Spalding (1st Movement, Part 1), undated; bell_brothers_277; shellac disc
  - Mozart: Sonata in E Flat Major, Spalding (1st Movement, Part 2), undated; bell_brothers_278; shellac disc
  - Mozart: Sonata in E Flat Major, Spalding (2nd Movement), undated; bell_brothers_279; shellac disc
  - Mozart: Sonata in E Flat Major, Spalding (3rd Movement), undated; bell_brothers_280; shellac disc
  - Museum of Modern Arts: Villa-Lobos: Bachianas Brasileiras, No. 1, Finale Fugue, undated; bell_brothers_423; shellac disc
  - Museum of Modern Arts: Villa-Lobos: Nonetto for Chamber orchestra and Chorus, undated; bell_brothers_424; shellac disc
  - Music America Loves Best (No. 75), 11/11/1945; bell_brothers_511; vinyl disc
  - Music for Sunday, Art Baker (Series H-6, No. 62), undated; bell_brothers_482; vinyl disc
  - Music from America (No. 103), 10/23/1944; bell_brothers_474; vinyl disc
  - Music Library: Freddie Nagel and His Orchestra; Loumell Morgan Trio (No. P-57 and P-58), undated; bell_brothers_510; vinyl disc
  - Music Library: Loumell Morgan Trio (No. P-59 and P-60), undated; bell_brothers_463; vinyl disc
  - Music Library: Singing Strings (No. C-11 and C-12), undated; bell_brothers_487; vinyl disc
  - Music on Deck: Carmen Cavallaro and Jerry Sourthern (No. 17 and 18), undated; bell_brothers_499; vinyl disc
  - Mussorgsky: A Night on the Bare Mountain, Stokowski (Part 1), undated; bell_brothers_417; shellac disc
  - Mussorgsky: A Night on the Bare Mountain, Stokowski (Part 2), undated; bell_brothers_418; shellac disc
  - Mussorgsky: Picture at an Exhibition, Stokowski and Philadelphia Orchestra (Part 1), 11/27/1939; bell_brothers_410; shellac disc
  - Mussorgsky: Picture at an Exhibition, Stokowski and Philadelphia Orchestra (Part 2), 11/27/1939; bell_brothers_411; shellac disc
  - Mussorgsky: Picture at an Exhibition, Stokowski and Philadelphia Orchestra (Part 3), 11/27/1939; bell_brothers_412; shellac disc
  - Mussorgsky: Picture at an Exhibition, Stokowski and Philadelphia Orchestra (Part 4), 11/27/1939; bell_brothers_413; shellac disc
  - Mussorgsky: Picture at an Exhibition, Stokowski and Philadelphia Orchestra (Part 5), 11/27/1939; bell_brothers_414; shellac disc
  - Mussorgsky: Picture at an Exhibition, Stokowski and Philadelphia Orchestra, Mr. O'Connell (Part 6), 11/27/1939; bell_brothers_415; shellac disc
  - Mussorgsky: Picture at an Exhibition, Stokowski and Philadelphia Orchestra (Part 7), 11/27/1939; bell_brothers_416; shellac disc
  - My Enchanting Senorita, undated; bell_brothers_142; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - My Secret Love Is You; Ebb Tide, undated; bell_brothers_075; lacquer on glass disc
  - Navy Swing and Sway Time, featuring Sammy Kaye and His Orchestra (No. 1A and 2A), 09/23/1950; 09/30/1950; bell_brothers_496; vinyl disc
  - Navy Swing and Sway Time, featuring Sammy Kaye and His Orchestra (No. 5A-6A), 10/21/1950; 10/28/1950; bell_brothers_497; vinyl disc
  - Navy Swing and Sway Time, featuring Sammy Kaye and His Orchestra (No. 9A-10A), 11/18/1950; 11/25/1950; bell_brothers_498; vinyl disc
  - Navy Swing and Sway Time, featuring Sammy Kaye and His Orchestra (No. 13A-14A), undated; bell_brothers_580; vinyl disc
  - NBC Symphony Orchestra, Arturo Toscanini (Parts 1 and 2), 02/17/1951; bell_brothers_254; vinyl disc
  - NBC Symphony Orchestra, Arturo Toscanini (Parts 1 and 2), 02/03/1951; bell_brothers_255; vinyl disc
  - NEC Radio Series, United States Government Reports: Cabinet Series: President Roosevelt and Lowell Mellett, NEC Director (No. 1), 05/09/1939; bell_brothers_691; vitrolac disc
  - Oh! Ka-Ka!; Ang Harana Ni Tembong, undated; bell_brothers_079; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - One Million B. C., staring Victor Mature, Carole Landis, Lon Chaney, Jr., undated; bell_brothers_035; vinyl disc
  - One Night Stand, Cootie Williams and Orchestra (No. 582), 02/12/1945; bell_brothers_524; vinyl disc
  - One Night Stand, Sid Hoff (No. 610), 02/24/1945; bell_brothers_611; vinyl disc
  - One Night Stand, Ted Fioreto (No. 393), 10/08/1944; bell_brothers_485; vinyl disc
  - One Night Stand, Woody Herman (No. 550), 11/14/1944; bell_brothers_525; vinyl disc
  - Overture to a Comic Opera - Saint Saens (Part 1), 04/30/1943; bell_brothers_214; lacquer on glass disc
  - Paderewski: Symphony in B Minor (Parts 1 and 3), 01/20/1940; bell_brothers_187; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Page Morton: He Wears a Pair of Silver Wings (Part 3); My Devotion, 08/31/1942; bell_brothers_113; lacquer on glass disc
  - Palesrina: Missa Brevis: Credo Trapp Choir (Part 3), undated; bell_brothers_256; shellac disc
  - Pasikat; S. S. B., undated; bell_brothers_077; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Pasquale Amato, 04/14/1913; 04/18/1913; bell_brothers_067; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Patty O’Connor: Only Heaven Knows; Jay Johnston: Day By Day, 03/08/1946; bell_brothers_145; lacquer on glass disc
  - Percy Faith and Mitch Miller: Sam’s Song, undated; bell_brothers_229; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Perry Como: 1 and 2 - Ideal Gossip; 1 - Anchors Aweigh (Film, 1945); 2 - Geraldine Brooks: Aida - Ritorna Vincitor; 3 - Faustino Santalices (Romances Gallegos): Romance De Don Gaiferos (Siglo XII); 4 - Camina Don Sancho: Axeitame A Polainima), Eng. Col. En. 1107, Part 5, undated; bell_brothers_233; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Personal Album, Ginny Simms; Jo Stafford (Series H-3, No. 641-642), undated; bell_brothers_526; vinyl disc
  - Personal Album, Lou Lee Norman and Margaret Whiting; (No. 445 and 446), undated; bell_brothers_491; vinyl disc
  - Pieta, Signore - preghiera, Rosalia Chalia and Orchestra, undated; bell_brothers_224; lacquer on glass disc
  - Prelude De La Suite Persane; Bayate Isphahan, undated; bell_brothers_082; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Quiz Kids (No. 10), undated; bell_brothers_630; vinyl disc
  - Rabbi Jacob Joseph School (Parts 5 and 6), undated; bell_brothers_046; lacquer on glass disc
  - Rabbi Jacob Joseph School (Parts 7 and 8), undated; bell_brothers_053; lacquer on glass disc
  - Rabbi Jacob Joseph School (Part 10), undated; bell_brothers_047; lacquer on glass disc
  - Rachmaninoff: Concerto No. 1 in F Sharp Minor (Part 1); Arensky: Overture Dream of [sic] the Volga (Part 1), undated; bell_brothers_050; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Rachmaninoff: Concerto No. 1 in F Sharp Minor (Part 2); Arensky: Overture Dream of [sic] the Volga (Part 2), undated; bell_brothers_051; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Ralph Flanagan: [Title is illegible]; Pink Champagne, undated; bell_brothers_091; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Ralph Flanagan: It Isn’t Fair; Tex Beneke: Rhapsody In Blue, undated; bell_brothers_093; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Ralph Flanagan: Red River Valley; Age Negra, undated; bell_brothers_094; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Ralph Flanagan: Toreador [sic]; Down The Line, undated; bell_brothers_095; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Ralph Flanagan: Toreador Song; Down The Line, undated; bell_brothers_092; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Ralph Flanagan: Washing Machine; Dancing Tambourine, undated; bell_brothers_084; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Ravel: Le Paon, Frijsh, undated; bell_brothers_288; vitrolac disc
  - Raymond Massey Familiar Reading From the Bible; Ken Griffin At The Hammond Organ, Monica Lewis With Mack Stewart Quartet (WPS Record 211), undated; bell_brothers_787; vinyl disc
  - Raymond Scott (No. 3); Band Wagon (No. 88), undated; bell_brothers_608; vinyl disc
  - Raymond Scott (No. 156-157), 10/24/1944; bell_brothers_522; vinyl disc
  - Rieti: Sonata (Parts 1 and 3), undated; bell_brothers_192; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Rieti: Sonata (Parts 2 and 4), undated; bell_brothers_193; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Rigoletto, monolog Tito Xirelli; Serenata [sic]: Xirelli, Vidalis Valeris, undated; bell_brothers_202; on shellac disc
  - Robert Maxwell, undated; bell_brothers_065; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Romeo and Juliet (Parts 1 and 2), undated; bell_brothers_732; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Romeo and Juliet (Parts 3 and 4), undated; bell_brothers_733; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Ropartz: Pastorale and Dance, for Oboe and Orchestra, Wallenstein; Philharmonic Society: Cesar Frank [sic]: Tone Poem, Arturo Toscanini, 03/15/1936; bell_brothers_194; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Roy Shield and Co. Replacing Melody (Hour 56), 10/03/1944; bell_brothers_488; vinyl disc
  - Rubinstein: Dance from Feramors; Rinskey-Korsakoff: Suite from Tzar Saltan (Part 2), 04/19/1942; bell_brothers_215; lacquer on glass disc
  - Rubinstein: Quartet in F Major, Op. 55 (Part 1); Glinka: Trio Pathetique, (Part 1), undated; bell_brothers_179; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Rubinstein: Quartet in F Major, Op. 55 (Parts 3 and 5), undated; bell_brothers_181; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Rubinstein: Quartet in F Major, Op. 55 (Parts 4 and 6), undated; bell_brothers_182; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Rubinstein: Quartet in F Major, Op. 55, (Part 2); Glinka: Trio Pathetique, (Part 2), undated; bell_brothers_180; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Russ Columbo, undated; bell_brothers_038; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Salubert [sic]: Piano Sonata; Artur Schnabel at Town Hall (Parts 1 and 3), undated; bell_brothers_176; lacquer on glass disc
  - Schubert: Gruppe aus dem Tartarus, Frijsh, undated; bell_brothers_289; on vitrolac disc
  - Schubert: Piano Sonata; Artur Schnabel at Town Hall, (Parts 2 and 4), undated; bell_brothers_177; lacquer on glass disc
  - Schumann: Three Schumann songs, Frijsh, undated; bell_brothers_290; vitrolac disc
  - Schumann: Two Grenadiers, Kipnis, undated; bell_brothers_291; vitrolac disc
  - Serenade for Strings; Swingtime, Armed Forces Swing Band, Mel Torme (Series H-51, No. 29), undated; bell_brothers_615; vinyl disc
  - Serenade in Blue (No. 163-164), 03/28/1954; 04/18/1954; bell_brothers_550; vinyl disc
  - Serenade in Blue (No. 167-168), 04/25/1954; 05/16/1954; bell_brothers_551; vinyl disc
  - Serenade in Blue (No. 169-170), 05/23/1954; 06/13/1954; bell_brothers_552; vinyl disc
  - Serenade in Blue (No. 171-172), 05/23/1954; 06/13/1954; bell_brothers_553; vinyl disc
  - Serenade in Blue (No. 173-174), 06/20/1954; 07/11/1954; bell_brothers_554; vinyl disc
  - Serenade in Blue (No. 175-176), 06/20/1954; 07/11/1954; bell_brothers_555; vinyl disc
  - Serenade in Blue (No. 177-178), 07/18/1954; 08/08/1954; bell_brothers_556; vinyl disc
  - Serenade in Blue (No. 179-180), 07/18/1954; 07/25/1954; 08/08/1954; bell_brothers_557; vinyl disc
  - Serenade in Blue (No. 181-182), 08/15/1954; 09/05/1954; bell_brothers_558; vinyl disc
  - Serenade in Blue (No. 183-184), 08/15/1954; 09/05/1954; bell_brothers_559; vinyl disc
  - Serenade in Blue (No. 191-192), 10/10/1954; 10/31/1954; bell_brothers_560; vinyl disc
  - Serenade in Blue (No. 197-198), 12/05/1954; 12/26/1954; bell_brothers_561; vinyl disc
  - Serenade in Blue (No. 221-222), 05/22/1955; 06/12/1955; bell_brothers_562; vinyl disc
  - Serenade in Blue (No. 229-230), 07/17/1955; 08/07/1955; bell_brothers_563; vinyl disc
  - Serenade in Blue (No. 231-232), 07/17/1955; 08/07/1955; bell_brothers_564; vinyl disc
  - Serenade in Blue (No. 237-238), 09/11/1955; 10/02/1955; bell_brothers_565; vinyl disc
  - Serenade in Blue (No. 291-292), 09/10/1956; 10/01/1956; bell_brothers_619; vinyl disc
  - Serenade in Blue (No. 301-302), 12/02/1956; 12/09/1956; bell_brothers_620; vinyl disc
  - Serenade in Blue (No. 307-308), 01/20/1957; 01/27/1957; bell_brothers_621; vinyl disc
  - Serenade in Blue (No. 325-326), 05/26/1957; 06/02/1957; bell_brothers_622; vinyl disc
  - Serenade in Blue (No. 331-332), 07/07/1957; 07/14/1957; bell_brothers_623; vinyl disc
  - Serenade in Blue (No. 333-334), 07/21/1957; 07/28/1957; bell_brothers_624; vinyl disc
  - Serenade in Blue (No. 339-340), 09/08/1957; bell_brothers_625; vinyl disc
  - Serenade in Blue (No. 341-342), 09/15/1957; 09/22/1957; bell_brothers_549; vinyl disc
  - Serenade in Blue (No. 343-344), 09/29/1957; 10/06/1957; bell_brothers_626; vinyl disc
  - Sexteto Habanero, undated; bell_brothers_072; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Sexteto Habanero; Sexteto Machin, undated; bell_brothers_071; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Sgambati: Symphony No. 1 in D Major, Op. 16 (Part 2), 09/01/1941; bell_brothers_155; lacquer on glass disc
  - Sgambati: Symphony No. 1 in D Major, Op. 16 (Parts 1 and 3), 09/01/1941; bell_brothers_154; lacquer on glass disc
  - Shine On, Harvest Moon (Part 1 and 2), undated; bell_brothers_057; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Shine On, Harvest Moon (Part 3), undated; bell_brothers_058; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Shostakovich: Concert For Piano (Part 2); Toeschi: Symphony In D. (Part 2), undated; bell_brothers_041; lacquer on glass disc